SUMMER J. KEREKES

(513) 290-2582 www.linkedin.com/in/summer-kerekes

<u>summerkerekes@gmail.com</u> https://trailblazer.me/id/skerekes

Summary

Army veteran and professional with 25 years of customer support and IT experience looking to translate service orientation and people skills into a career as a Salesforce/JavaScript Developer. Recent graduate of Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder program with Salesforce Developer certification anticipated July 2021 and Expeditioner Trailhead rank.

Skills & Highlights

Preparing for Salesforce Developer Certification	Oracle Apex programming	Salesforce Lightning
C# / .NET Framework	ASP.NET Web MVC	Entity Framework
JavaScript, React	HTML5 / CSS3	Git / GitHub
Project Management	Unified Communications	PowerShell

Professional Experience

Eleven Fifty Academy - Indianapolis, IN

October 2020 – Present

Learning Assistant (contract)

 Explained fundamental coding concepts at length, assisted in teaching correct syntax over a breadth of programming languages (JavaScript, HTML and CSS) to 35+ students daily, remotely.

Concentrix (Convergys) - Cincinnati, OH

April 2009 - February 2019

Associate Programmer / Collaboration Specialist

June 2017 – February 2019

- Supported unified communications platform, Skype for Business (hybrid) for publicly traded, multinational organization of 225,000 located in 40+ countries with 19,000+ Skype for Business users.
- Provided end user information training, mentoring and knowledge transfer for audio-video solutions.
- O365 Administration of Skype for Business, MFA and Exchange
- Experience with: Skype for Business, Zoom, Blue Jeans, Cisco WebEx, Cisco Telepresence

Executive Administrator

April 2009 – June 2017

- Supported CIO and senior leadership for a publicly traded, multinational organization of 130,000 located in 33 countries with administrative duties, spanning Business Development, office of the Chief of Staff, Collections Licensing, Facilities Management, Global Brand and Communications, Global Technology Solutions, Market Strategy, and Mergers & Acquisitions.
- Managed high volume calendars, scheduling appointments and coordinating meetings
- Excelled at making detailed travel arrangements in Concur (domestic and international)
- Reconciled expenses in PeopleSoft Financials for executives and teams
- Managed special projects and delegated tasks
- Accomplished with Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint, Skype for Business and SharePoint

Wachovia - Blue Ash, OH

July 2006 - October 2007

Mortgage Consultant

- Collected sensitive information to assess a borrower's credit and financial history
- Worked with potential borrowers to get the best loan for their financial situation
- Provided high level of customer service, ensuring borrowers fully understood the process

Summer J. Kerekes Page 2

Philip Morris USA — Milford, OH

Section Management Assistant

- Processed national account invoicing and payment reconciliations
- Designed and wrote payment reconciliation guide that was adopted nationally
- Supported calendar management, large meeting coordination, and conducted financial audits
- Maintained records compliance (Sarbanes-Oxley)

Kelly Services - Indianapolis, IN

February 2000 – March 2003

August 2003 – April 2006

- Assigned various administrative and management support positions within Philip Morris USA, Eli Lilly & Co, and Sprint PCS.
- Office management
- HR Recruiting
- Customer Service Management
- Marketing & Sales Support

Education

IUPUI - Indianapolis, IN

2000

Associate's Degree in General Studies

New Horizons Computer Learning Centers – Blue Ash, OH

Automating Administration with Windows PowerShell Core Solutions of Microsoft Skype for Business 2015 June 2018 October 2017

Eleven Fifty Academy - Indianapolis, IN

Software Development, C#, .NET Web Development, JavaScript, React April 2020 – July 2020 July 2020 – October 2020

Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder Program

October 2020 - February 2021

Developer Certification

- Salesforce and Deloitte joint program to build Salesforce Developer and business soft skills which provides 100+ hours of Salesforce technical training
- Advanced technical skills include: Data management (incl. data modeling, security and data access), automation using workflow rules and process builder, and reports / dashboards

Certifications

HTML and CSS Foundations, https://bit.ly/3fAgTfW

April 2020

Software Development Boot Camp, https://bit.ly/JewelInventory

July 2020

Web Development Boot Camp, portfolio

October 2020

Military Experience/Education

United States Army

August 1993 - May 1996

United States Army Reserve

June 1996 - May 1999

- Installed, operated, maintained, and troubleshot communication equipment systems
- Served in Operation Restore Hope, Haiti 1994 and Korea 1995 1996
- Security Clearance: Secret (1993 2003)

Leadership & Community Experience

- 8+ gallon plasma / platelet donor
- Mallards of Mason Condominium Board of Directors,

2007 - 2019

- CityLink Center, facilitated and taught computer literacy and basic skills
- Fresh Start of Indianapolis, trained Domestic Violence survivors in basic computing concepts, MS Office, internet and email systems